Rin.
What do you want to get from Santa?
I haven't decided yet.
If you don't think of something fast, it might be too late.
He's coming from somewhere really far away.
Oh yeah...
Hey, hey. What's the thing you want the most?
Lop ear!
What's that?
Her best friend.
Good evening.
Sorry...
I'm really late...
It's okay.
Rin-chan!
What's that?
A Christmas tree.
And this?
Well... it's stuff from work...
Can we set up the tree?
Daikichi, hurry up!
Okay.
This goes on top?
That's right.
What happened?
Our house doesn't have a chimney.
Santa will find a way. It'll be okay!
Then I'll leave the doors unlocked!
It's okay.
To Santa
Thanks for
the present.
What's with this carrot?
It's for the reindeers.
Can I turn it off?
Just a little longer...
Santa won't come if you don't go to sleep.
Hurry up and turn it off!
Okay, okay...
To Santa
Thanks for
the present.
Rin
I also wanted to meet you, Santa.
Rin, let's eat.
Okay!
Thank you too, reindeer!